Andrés David Solarte Vidal

Email address: soy@andresdavidsv.com Cell: (+57) 3043 738 746

Santiago de Cali, Colombia

Willing to relocate

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andresdavidsv/

Professional profile

I'm a Mobile Software Engineer with more than 4 years of experience in the industry. In my spare time, I am also a professional triathlete. During my time in the tech industry, I have had the opportunity to master multiple programming languages such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, PHP and SQL, and different tools such as React, Nextjs, React Native, Nestjs and Vuejs. I have participated in diverse projects across multiple industries and with multicultural teams.

Technical skills

Tools:

Visual Studio Code - Xcode - Android Studio - Laragon - MySQL - MariaDB - Postgresql

Programming languages:

JavaScript - React Native - React - React Native - NextJs - NestJs - TypeScript - AWS - Vue - Angular - TailwindCSS - Java - PHP - Laravel - Python - SQL - Graphql

Education

2014 - 2020 Pontificia Universidad Javeriana Cali

Electronic Engineering

Professional experience

Mobile Software Engineer - Software Engineer

Autonomo

Jul 2022 – Actually

- Develop custom React applications
- Develop custom React Native applications

Cafeto SoftwareSAS

Software Engineer

- Develop custom Vue applications.
- Provide Full Stack support to web applications made in Angular on the
- FrontEnd and Node.js with Graphql on the BackEnd
 Provide support to mobile applications made in React Native

Macrolite SAS

Developer

Dec 2020 - Mar 2021

Mar 2021 - Jul 2022

Develop custom WordPress applications, including Laravel framework.

IT Efectivos

Support Engineer

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

Provide support during the migration of 6 applications, filling the necessary documentation with the respective user manuals and UATs.

Turbo Transportes AV S.A.S

Management Assistant

Jan 2020 - Aug 2020

• Implement the use of technologies for the company's data processing, creating a website, formats and work platforms with data bases.

Transporte Continental Agencia Cali6

Logistics Assistant

Jan 2016 - Jul 2020

Contributing in the creation and implementation of a desktop application for the consumption of a web service, producing a 20% improvement in work flow times.

Other

Publishings Desarrollo de un AGV modular para la integración de sistema de Manufactura

(2020)

Database Administrator – Fundación Carlos Slim Frontend Developer – Fundación Carlos Slim

Training Laravel and Vue – UDEMY

FrontEnd Web Development with Vue.js - Platzi PHP Backend Web Development – Platzi

FrontEnd Architecture – Platzi React Native – Coder House

Desarrollador Backend - Coder House

Escuela de JavaScript - Platzi

FullStack Development – Acamica

React Native - Coder House

Languages Spanish (Native), English (B1)